University Photograph; Collection ua390
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated